buffyguide.com 2018-12-14

# Privacy Policy - BuffyGuide.com

BuffyGuide.com — The Complete Buffy Episode Guide  
---  
Privacy Policy  

**Collected Information and Use**

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site.

We use cookies to limit the number of popup ads that you may see while visiting our site. We use cookies in the forums to track your login and deliver pages customized to your preferences.

When contacting us via the contact forms on our website, an email address is required. This is used to respond to your message.

When signing up for our newsletter (mailing list), an email address is required. This is used to send the newsletter emails to you.

When registering for our forums, a valid email address is required to register. This is used to send you your password when you register, to send you your password again if you should ever forget it, to notify you of replies or private messages if you enable these options, and for the administration to email you with important information if necessary.

BuffyGuide.com will not rent, sell, or give away any email addresses subscribed to our mailing list, registered at our forums, or provided when contacting us via any method; nor will we rent, sell, or give away any other personal information you may supply to us.

BuffyGuide.com will not disclose your name, email address or any other personal details supplied by you except in the following circumstances:  
    a) You agree that we may pass on your details or disclose your identifying data, other information or content to any law enforcement or regulatory authority in order to comply with their direction or request in regard to legal process,  
    b) You further agree that we may disclose your identifying data, other information or content to a third party in response to any claim of aggrievement or claim of violation of a third party's rights.

**Opting Out**

If you are subscribed to our newsletter (mailing list), you can unsubscribe at any time, and your email address will not be saved or used in any way. Every newsletter you receive will have instructions on how to unsubscribe.

If you are registered for our forums, you can request at any time to have your forum registration deleted. This will cause all of your related personal information to be deleted from the database, including your contact email address, none of which will be saved or used in any way. Note that having your registration deleted does NOT delete any posts or messages you made while registered. If you wish to delete any contents of your posts, you should do so BEFORE requesting to have your registration deleted.

**Other Sites**

This site contains links to other sites. BuffyGuide.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web Sites.

BuffyGuide.com may use outside advertising companies to display advertisements anywhere on this website. These advertisements may contain cookies. 

**Third Party Advertising**

We use Gorilla Nation, DoubleClick and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (NOT including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

This website may utilize certain services provided by DoubleClick, Inc. (DoubleClick). For further information concerning DoubleClick's privacy practices, including the ability to opt-out from any data collection, reporting and/or targeting activities associated with its services, please go to <http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/>

From time to time some of our advertising partners may prompt you to enter your email address or other personal information via an ad on this site. Please refer to their privacy policy for their specific use of this information.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.

Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting aboutads.info.)

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party ad server, Gorilla Nation, DoubleClick or their affiliates, or individual advertisers may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. Any cookies received with banner or other ads are collected by these advertising companies, and BuffyGuide.com does not have any control over or access to this information and will not be held liable for the use of these cookies.

**Protection of Data**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. While there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet, we will take all reasonable steps to insure the safety of your personal information. All of the data regarding users, in relation to forum registration, are stored on a server. That server is owned and hosted by Rackspace.com, and leased by BuffyGuide.com. This server is located in a locked and guarded space and only authorized Rackspace personnel have physical access to it. Only the BuffyGuide.com webmaster, and authorized Rackspace personnel, have remote access to the server and the data stored on it.

**Forums**

If you are registered for our forums, you may wish to read the forum privacy policy [here](http://forums.buffyguide.com/instructions/instructions_01.shtml#privacy).

**Contacting BuffyGuide.com**

[ ](http://www.monkeys.com/spammers-are-leeches/) [ ](http://www.buffyguide.com/mail/harfest/) If you have any questions or comments about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact [bguide@buffyguide.com](mailto:bguide@buffyguide.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy) .
